https://www.kayakdoorcounty.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Who we are
Here at Kayak Door County, we are committed to maintaining the trust and confidence of visitors to our web site. We are not in the business of selling, renting or trading email lists and other personal information with other companies for marketing purposes.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymous string is created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
Contact forms are used on our website for the purpose of collecting inquiries from potential and current clients. We request as little information from you to be able to follow up on inquires an not probe too far into your personal information. Some of this information may be retained in order to follow up on future inquires.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Cookies are also used on this website to target ads using the Facebook Pixel.
Embedded content from other websites
This site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics information
This website uses Google Analytics and the Facebook Pixel to track general information on visits to our site. This information is then used to create a better experience for visitors to our site. Information may also be used to promote our services on various platforms such as Facebook.
Who we share your data with
Any information we collect is used within our organization only and not shared with other business unless you give us permission to do so. Kayak Door County is not responsible for the content or the privacy of websites to which it may link.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
Google Analytics user and data is retained for a period of 38 months.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service before being posted to our site.
Our contact information
Kayak Door County59 N Madison Ave.Sturgeon Bay, WI 54235julie@kayakdoorcounty.com
Follow all the fun we’re having!
Get the latest on gear & classes
Join Our Email List
